[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "What does FBLA stand for?",
        "options": [
            "Future Blooming Leaders of America",
            "Future Business Leaders of America",
            "Future Bundle Leaders of America",
            "Future Business Leaders of Austria"
        ],
        "answer": "Future Business Leaders of America"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: FBLA holds regional competitions",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "Fill in the missing word: Future ________ Leaders of America",
        "answer": "business"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are true about FBLA-PBL? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "Has the BAA program",
            "It is a college program",
            "It is a high school program",
            "It has an entry fee of $150"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "Has the BAA program",
            "It is a high school program",
            "It is a college program"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "What is the full form of the BAA?",
        "answer": "business achievement awards"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the events to their type",
        "options": [
            "A) Solo test",
            "B) Individual",
            "C) Teams of up to three"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Cyber Security",
            "Introduction to Social Media Strategy",
            "Impromptu Speaking",
            "Introduction to Business",
            "Digital Video Production"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Cyber Security": "A",
            "Introduction to Social Media Strategy": "C",
            "Impromptu Speaking": "B",
            "Introduction to Business": "A",
            "Digital Video Production": "C"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "What state is FBLA-PBL headquartered in?",
        "options": [
            "Virginia",
            "Washington",
            "Maryland",
            "California"
        ],
        "answer": "Virginia"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: FBLA was founded over 100 years ago",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "The name of the founder of FBLA-PBL was: Hamden L. _______",
        "answer": "forkner"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are divisions of FBLA-PBL? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "FBLA",
            "FBLA-ML",
            "FBLA-Professional Division",
            "FBLA-College Program"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "FBLA",
            "FBLA-ML"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "Current president and CEO of FBLA-PBL (first and last name)",
        "answer": "alexander graham"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the events to their category",
        "options": [
            "A) Presentation",
            "B) Report",
            "C) Speech"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Business Ethics",
            "Business Plan",
            "Public Speaking",
            "Client Service",
            "Impromptu Speaking"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Business Ethics": "A",
            "Business Plan": "B",
            "Public Speaking": "C",
            "Client Service": "A",
            "Impromptu Speaking": "C"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "How many people are enrolled in FBLA?",
        "options": [
            "More than 200,000",
            "More than 150,000",
            "More than 80,000",
            "More than 50,000"
        ],
        "answer": "More than 200,000"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: The FBLA is one of the top 10 organizations listed by the US Dept of Education",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "The full form of PBL is: Phi ____ Lambda",
        "answer": "beta"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "FBLA is present in which countries? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "India",
            "Canada",
            "Hungary",
            "Kazakhstan"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "Canada",
            "Hungary",
            "Kazakhstan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "What is the full name of FBLA's college division?",
        "answer": "phi beta lambda"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the descriptions to their BAA level",
        "options": [
            "A) Future",
            "B) Leader",
            "C) Business"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Business skills and introduction to community service",
            "emphasis on regional FBLA involement and community leadership",
            "advanced business skills",
            "national FBLA involvement, and focus on becoming community leaders",
            "emphasizes the importance of getting involved with FBLA locally"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Business skills and introduction to community service": "A",
            "emphasis on regional FBLA involement and community leadership": "C",
            "advanced business skills": "B",
            "national FBLA involvement, and focus on becoming community leaders": "B",
            "emphasizes the importance of getting involved with FBLA locally": "A"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "How many people can participate in the Computer Game and Simulation Programming event as a group?",
        "options": [
            "Up to 4",
            "Up to 3",
            "Up to 2",
            "Only 1"
        ],
        "answer": "Up to 3"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: There are 5 levels of the BAA",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "Level one of the BAA is: ______",
        "answer": "future"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which BAA events have their deadline on March 1? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "Service",
            "Leader",
            "Business",
            "America"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "Leader",
            "Business"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "What is the core concept of the BAA which focuses on improving a member's school?",
        "answer": "service"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the required activity to the associated BAA award",
        "options": [
            "A) Future",
            "B) Business",
            "C) America"
        ],
        "words": [
            "5 hours of community service",
            "Video promoting a competitive event",
            "Flyer promoting FBLA",
            "75 hours of community service",
            "Get a letter of recommendation about your leadership skills"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "5 hours of community service": "A",
            "Video promoting a competitive event": "B",
            "Flyer promoting FBLA": "A",
            "75 hours of community service": "C",
            "Get a letter of recommendation about your leadership skills": "C"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "What attire must be worn to FBLA events?",
        "options": [
            "Formal",
            "Business Casual",
            "Casual",
            "Flip-Flops"
        ],
        "answer": "Business Casual"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: 'Knowledge' is one of the core concepts of the BAA",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "The _____ ______ Chapter Challenge has chapters complete 10 tasks revolving around recruitment",
        "answer": "super sweeps"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are additional FBLA programs? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "National Awards program",
            "Adviser Wall of Fame",
            "Forkner award",
            "Sweep Stakes challenge"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "National Awards program",
            "Adviser Wall of Fame"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "At which event are national officers elected?",
        "answer": "national leadership conference"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the American Enterprise Day activites to the level at which they would be organized",
        "options": [
            "A) Elementary Schools",
            "B) Middle/High School",
            "C) College/Uniersity"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Organize a panel of experts to discuss the pros and cons of owning a business",
            "Assign essays on the American enterprise system",
            "Present songs and skits about American enterprise",
            "Design a workbook about filling out job applications and the different occupations possible",
            "Sponsor a 5 month forum on American enterprise, spanning multiple topics"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Organize a panel of experts to discuss the pros and cons of owning a business": "C",
            "Assign essays on the American enterprise system": "B",
            "Present songs and skits about American enterprise": "A",
            "Design a workbook about filling out job applications and the different occupations possible": "B",
            "Sponsor a 5 month forum on American enterprise, spanning multiple topics": "C"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "How many years of service must one have to be eligible for the FBLA-PBL Adviser Hall of Fame?",
        "options": [
            "10",
            "15",
            "20",
            "25"
        ],
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: You can take a maximum of 3 objective tests in Regionals",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "Fill in the missing word: ______ Business Leaders of America",
        "answer": "future"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are core FBLA goals? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "Strengthen the confidence of students",
            "Develop character",
            "Invest into stocks for profit",
            "Encourage and practice efficient money management"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "Strengthen the confidence of students",
            "Develop character",
            "Encourage and practice efficient money management"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "Who is the current FBLA National President?",
        "answer": "drew lojewski"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the FBLA National Officer with the position they hold",
        "options": [
            "A) FBLA National President",
            "B) FBLA National Parliamentarian",
            "C) FBLA Regional Vice President"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Kianna Bolante",
            "Maria Manabat",
            "Rhea Mehta",
            "Drew Lojewski",
            "Andrew Fox"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Kianna Bolante": "B",
            "Maria Manabat": "C",
            "Rhea Mehta": "C",
            "Drew Lojewski": "A",
            "Andrew Fox": "C"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "When is American Enterprise Day?",
        "options": [
            "December 1",
            "November 15",
            "July 5",
            "August 23"
        ],
        "answer": "November 15"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: Indiana was the FBLA state chapter",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "Fill in the missing word: Future Business _______ of America",
        "answer": "leaders"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are adherent to the FBLA-PBL creed? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "education is the right of every person",
            "every person has the right to earn a living at a useful occupation",
            "businesses growth must be pursued at all costs",
            "I promise to use my abilities to make the world a better place for everyone."
        ],
        "answer": [
            "education is the right of every person",
            "every person has the right to earn a living at a useful occupation",
            "I promise to use my abilities to make the world a better place for everyone."
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "Who is the current FBLA Western Region Vice President?",
        "answer": "sachin sundar"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the sponsor with its category",
        "options": [
            "A) Member Discounts and Added Benefits",
            "B) Education and Leadership",
            "C) Fundraising"
        ],
        "words": [
            "GEICO",
            "Crimson Education",
            "Wyndham Hotel Group",
            "Country Meats",
            "BETA Camp"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "GEICO": "A",
            "Crimson Education": "B",
            "Wyndham Hotel Group": "A",
            "Country Meats": "C",
            "BETA Camp": "B"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "What is February 15 in FBLA-PBL Week?",
        "options": [
            "Each One Reach One Day",
            "Webinar: National Presidents' Forum",
            "Career Awareness Day",
            "Community Service Day"
        ],
        "answer": "Future Business Leaders of America"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: FBLA's headquarters are in Richmond, VA",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "type": "blank",
        "question": "Fill in the missing word: Future Business Leaders of _______",
        "answer": "america"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which of the following are included in the FBLA Code of Ethics? (Choose all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "be honest and sincere.",
            "abide by the rules and regulations of my school",
            "take tasks with caution, questioning your skill",
            "wear business casual to school everyday"
        ],
        "answer": [
            "be honest and sincere.",
            "abide by the rules and regulations of my school"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "type": "saq",
        "question": "Who is the current FBLA National Treasurer?",
        "answer": "haneol lee"
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "type": "matching",
        "question": "Match the states to the administrative region they fall under",
        "options": [    
            "A) Western Region",
            "B) Southern Region",
            "C) Mountain Plains Region"
        ],
        "words": [
            "Arizona",
            "Tennessee",
            "New Mexico",
            "Washington",
            "Florida"
        ],
        "answer": {
            "Arizona": "A",
            "Tennessee": "B",
            "New Mexico": "C",
            "Washington": "A",
            "Florida": "B"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "type": "mcq",
        "question": "Which organization is FBLA's national charity partner?",
        "options": [
            "Salvation Army",
            "YMCA of the USA",
            "March of Dimes",
            "Step Up for Students"
        ],
        "answer": "March of Dimes"
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "type": "tf",
        "question": "True/False: The 2021 NLC will be held virtually",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    }
]
